import { Quiz, QuizQuestion } from '../../types';

const AdverbsOfTimeQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    description: 'Jaké slovo říkám?',
    name: 'Příslovce času',
    questions: [
      {
        answer: ['soon'],
        question: 'brzy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['often'],
        question: 'často'
      },
      {
        answer: ['long', 'long time'],
        question: 'dlouho'
      },
      {
        answer: ['immediately'],
        question: 'ihned'
      },
      {
        answer: ['still'],
        question: 'ještě'
      },
      {
        answer: ['already'],
        question: 'již'
      },
      {
        answer: ['briefly'],
        question: 'krátko'
      },
      {
        answer: ['this year'],
        question: 'letos'
      },
      {
        answer: ['last year'],
        question: 'loni'
      },
      {
        answer: ['forever'],
        question: 'navždy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['recently'],
        question: 'nedávno'
      },
      {
        answer: ['sometimes'],
        question: 'někdy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['never'],
        question: 'nikdy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['now'],
        question: 'nyni'
      },
      {
        answer: ['usually'],
        question: 'obvykle'
      },
      {
        answer: ['later'],
        question: 'později'
      },
      {
        answer: ['day after tomorrow'],
        question: 'pozítří'
      },
      {
        answer: ['day before yesterday'],
        question: 'předevčírem'
      },
      {
        answer: ['occasionally'],
        question: 'příležitostně'
      },
      {
        answer: ['already'],
        question: 'už'
      },
      {
        answer: ['always'],
        question: 'vždy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['yet'],
        question: 'zatím'
      },
      {
        answer: ['seldom'],
        question: 'zřídka'
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default AdverbsOfTimeQuiz;
